<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tim Novis</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tim Novis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 15:58:06 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 15:58:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About I&amp;rsquo;m Tim Novis, a web, JavaScript and aspiring ${language} developer from the South of England focussed on building UIs with React &amp;amp; React Native. Outside of programming, my interests mainly lie in music, amateur succulent growing, travel and eating way, way more than I should.
Currently daisie // Nov 2017 – Present
I&amp;rsquo;m currently working as lead UI engineer and technical director at daisie, a social media startup focussed on creating networking and collaboration tools for the next generation of creatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building to AppCenter from GitLab</title>
      <link>/post/building-to-appcenter-from-gitlab/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 16:39:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/building-to-appcenter-from-gitlab/</guid>
      <description>When I initially found out about AppCenter.ms, I was really excited to start using it, until, to my disappointment, I found that there was no support for GitLab. I didn&amp;rsquo;t stop there though!
I knew in order to get this working I&amp;rsquo;d have to use one of AppCenter&amp;rsquo;s supported git integrations, GitHub, BitBucket or VSTS. I knew I could mirror the repository from GitLab to one of these providers, and the most cost effective option seemed to be BitBucket as they have a great free plan for teams which allows private repositories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Aliases in React Native with Babel</title>
      <link>/post/custom-aliases-in-react-native-with-babel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 10:17:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/custom-aliases-in-react-native-with-babel/</guid>
      <description>Is there anything more infuriating than diving into a JavaScript project to find this?
import Component from &amp;#39;../../../some/deeply/ambiguous/location&amp;#39;;  Imagine if we could just import Component from &#39;myAlias/component&#39;; from anywhere in the codebase!
It&amp;rsquo;s super easy to set up - and there are a few ways to achieve it too.
1. With .babelrc If your project doesn&amp;rsquo;t use Webpack - for example if you&amp;rsquo;re working with React Native, you can use your .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017</title>
      <link>/post/2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 13:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2017/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; Highlights  I&amp;rsquo;ve worked at two great companies this year, the latter of which I&amp;rsquo;m super excited about. My programming skills have come by leaps and bounds since this time last year. I&amp;rsquo;ve been on two breaks to Rome and Sicily, and I&amp;rsquo;m going to Amsterdam in a few days time. I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered a load of great new music and podcasts. I&amp;rsquo;ve rewritten this website to use Hugo for static site generation, hosted on Netlify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November</title>
      <link>/post/november/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 13:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/november/</guid>
      <description>With a lot of deliberation, I left my previous job after being offered the opportunity to help build a new early stage startup from the ground up - I&amp;rsquo;m really excited about the new job, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot to get my teeth stuck into from product design all the way through to actually building the application, 2018&amp;rsquo;s shaping up to be a pretty interesting year. It also has to be said that I&amp;rsquo;m really enjoying working as part of what&amp;rsquo;s mainly a two-person team, definitely a welcome change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sicily</title>
      <link>/post/sicily/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 13:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/sicily/</guid>
      <description>Last week, I returned from a 10 day holiday in Sicily. We made two stops, in Ortigia &amp;amp; in Palermo.
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August Listening</title>
      <link>/post/august-listening/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 13:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/august-listening/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to some fantastic albums this month, some of which I haven&amp;rsquo;t listened to in a long while. A pleasant mix of odd, creepy folk music, strange Swedish electro &amp;amp; smooth jazzy tones.
Music  Timber Timbre - Timber Timbre Thievery Corporation - Radio Retaliation The Dining Rooms - Numero Deux Deerhunter - Halcyon Digest The Knife - Silent Shout  I&amp;rsquo;ve recently discovered The Guardian&amp;rsquo;s Audio Long Reads podcasts, they&amp;rsquo;re a great length and the content is often reallly interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>/post/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 13:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hello/</guid>
      <description>I needed a place to store my thoughts and record any work I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing, and my personal website was in dire need of a refresh.
I&amp;rsquo;ve kept it simple - at the time of writing, this website comes in to the browser at under 20kb. No client-side JavaScript, and the CSS is very minimal. You can find the code (and posts) for this website here.
~I was originally going to use a static site generator - whilst it would have been fun to learn about them, I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to conform to their way of doing things.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>